lingvo.ua 2012-07-22

# Privacy Policy

Your use of the Site and its Services are subject to your assent to the terms of the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. ABBYY may change the Privacy Policy, at its sole discretion, from time to time. By your continued use of the Site and its Services, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy, as well as, any subsequent changes. The meaning of certain capitalized terms are in the Terms of Use. 

**1\. Information Collection and Use.**

**A. What Are Some Types of Information That We Might Collect?**

ABBYY may: 

  * Collect information provided by you as your personal data in connection with registering yourself as a user of the Site and Services, i.e. your name, title, company name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address. 
  * Utilize "cookies", and other tracking technologies, that may record information such as Internet domain and host names, internet protocol (IP) addresses, Operating Systems, browser software, Clickstream data, and time frames of when the site is accessed. 
  * Record activities in connection with the Site and Services, such as requests for files, time of requests, and the IP address of the machine requesting the file. 
  * Collect Data files, including without limitation to the content of such files, including without limitation to text and images, that you upload and process through the Site and Services. 

**B. How We Might Use Information We Collect?**

Generally, ABBYY uses the information we collect to enable the operation of and improve our Site and Services, better meet customer needs, comply with applicable laws, and protect the rights of ABBYY, its users, and the public. For instance, we may use the information collected by ABBYY,

  * To record, support, and facilitate your participation in the activities you select and to prevent fraud and unlawful use. 
  * To determine your eligibility for technical support, contests or other benefits (if any). 
  * To track customer preferences, to provide a customized Site experience, 
  * To keep you informed about product upgrades, special offers, and other products and services of ABBYY unless such communications are prohibited by law or you have chosen not to receive such e-mail messages from ABBYY. You may remove Your e-mail address from ABBYY’s mailing list at any time.
  * To make the Site and Services easier to use by enabling the eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information.
  * To perform market research and analysis, and towards the improvement of our products, services, and technologies.
  * To enable the customization of content and advertising. 
  * To analyze trends relating to usage of the Site and Services, administer the site, track site movement, and gather non-individually identifying demographic information.
  * To respond to inquiries, such as to supply requested information on ABBYY products and services. 
  * To track and process orders placed with ABBYY authorized third parties. 
  * To protect and defend our rights and property, our services and/or users of our services, including the enforcement of our agreements or policies governing your use of the services.
  * To enforce the Terms of Use with respect to the Site and Services (including investigation of potential violations thereof).
  * To detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues.
  * To act on a good faith belief that such access or disclosure that it is legally required. 
  * To act on a good faith belief that it is necessary to protect the personal safety of ABBYY employees, customers or the public. 
  * To maintain accurate records of users of the Site and Service.

Information that is collected may also be disclosed to ABBYY’s partners, and/or third parties, such as contractors or service providers, in connection with the operation of the Site and the provision of Services (i.e. such as for processing payment, storage of the servers for the Site and Services). ABBYY may also share certain aggregated, non-personal information with third parties.

Additionally, the Sites web pages may include social media plugins. Usage of these plugins may allow social media services to use information about your browsing behaviour.

**2\. Our Mutual Responsibilities With Regarding To Your Information.**

It is our goal to use and handle information collected in a responsible manner. For one, we strive to limit our use of information that we collect as set forth herein. We also take measures to secure your information by physical, legal and technological means, such as storing your information on secure servers, located on premises that permit access to only authorized ABBYY personnel, encryption of data transfers, and protecting your accounts with passwords. In spite of such precautions, the security of your information cannot be absolutely guaranteed. First, we believe that no security system is impenetrable or fail-proof. 

Further, ABBYY cannot control what information you choose to upload, or your handling or treatment of your information. Therefore, you must exercise sound judgment with regard to what information you choose to upload, including without limitation to forming your own assessments as to the propriety, risks and sensitivities with regard to the information you transmit. You are also encouraged to take steps to secure your information, such as not divulging your password to others. 

By your use of the Site and Services, you agree that ABBYY will have no liability to you or any other party in connection with the information that you provide or is collected by ABBYY, including with limitation to any damages that may result from the handling or treatment of such information, and the disclosure or misuse of your information by third parties. You voluntarily and fully assume the risks for all consequences that relate to any and all information that you choose to upload or transfer. ABBYY assumes no obligation to ensure confidentiality or privacy of your information.

**3\. Location of Servers for the Site and Services.**

Your information may be stored and processed in any country in which ABBYY and its group and partner companies maintain facilities. In this regard, or for purposes of sharing or disclosing, ABBYY reserves the right to transfer information outside of your country. By using the Services, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country, for the purpose of enabling you to use the Services. As ABBYY continues to develop its business, ABBYY might sell or buy subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions as well as in the event ABBYY or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, personal information of the ABBYY Online Portal users will generally be one of the transferred business assets. We reserve the right to include your personal information, collected as an asset, in any such transfer to a third party. ABBYY, alone, has the right and sole discretion, to determine the location of the servers of the Site and Services.

**4\. Other Sites.**

The ABBYY website may contain links to other sites. We do not endorse or otherwise accept responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those sites.
